{
    "subject": "resource/Volkhard_Eitner",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "1996-11-05",
    "human_readable": "Volkhard Eitner died on November 5, 1996.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8690935373306274,
            "question": "When did Volkhard Eitner die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8008040189743042,
            "question": "Is November 5th a significant date for Volkhard Eitner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7601842880249023,
            "question": "How old was Volkhard Eitner when he died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7488970756530762,
            "question": "What is the date of Volkhard Eitner's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.69761723279953,
            "question": "Were there any notable events that happened around the time of Volkhard Eitner's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5319209098815918,
            "question": "In what year did Volkhard Eitner pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5254748463630676,
            "question": "Was Volkhard Eitner alive in the year 2000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4471081793308258,
            "question": "Can you provide any information about Volkhard Eitner's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43720924854278564,
            "question": "What field was Volkhard Eitner known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33810365200042725,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Volkhard Eitner's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Volkhard Eitner died on November 5, 1996.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5639_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field was Volkhard Eitner known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5639_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide any information about Volkhard Eitner's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5639_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Volkhard Eitner alive in the year 2000?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5639_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5639_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe document states that Volkhard Eitner's death date is given as November 5, 1996. Therefore, the statement \"Volkhard Eitner died on November 5, 1996\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}